Michael Adam Berry

web developer

Contact

Address

648 Manhattan Ave Brookyn, NY 11222

Email

me@adamberrv.dev

Phone

270.314.7807

website

adamberry.dev

Profile

A passionate technologist with a broad skill set, I create bespoke experiences on the web. I have extensive experience with HTML, CSS, Javascript and modern frameworks and libraries, but I believe my true strength as a developer lies in my ability to solve complex problems, learn new technologies quickly, and collaborate with teammembers, clients and managers. I strive to be a champion for a thriving, accessible and inclulsive internet and an active member of the New York City developer community. He/Him.

Experience

Open Source Web Developer

New York | 20017 - Present

- Developing open source web applications and data visualizations projects.
- Contributing to projects like 5Calls and Gatsby.

Web Developer

Freelance | New York City | 2019 - Present

- Creating websites for artists, writers, and small businesses
- Providing long term value by identifying the technologies for each clients specific needs.

Associate Project Manager

Seigfried's Basement Incorporated | New York | 2015-2019

 Assisting in the planning, construction, and installation of scenery for large scale live events throughout New York City. Clients included New York Fashion Week, Nike Pop-up Stores, and The Veuve Clicquot Polo Classic.

Actor

Film and Theatre - SAG | AEA | New York | 2009-2019

- Actor in films and plays in New York and regionally across the US.
 Noteable projects include A Birder's Guide To Everything (with Ben Kingsly), Private Romeo (LA Outfest Award for Best Ensemble)
- Founding Member of Exit Pursued By A Bear, a theatre company that remixes classic plays in a modern social environment.

Education

Bachelors of Fine Arts

Carnegie Mellon University 2005-2009

Certificate of Completion

Python for Data Science Coursera / University of Michigan

Certificate of Completion

CS50 / Intro to Computer Science EDX / Harvard University

Certificate of Completion

Advanced React
TylerMcquinnes.com

Skills

- HTML
- Node
- Three.js

- CSS
- Express
- SVG

- JavaScript
- D3
- Adobe Illustrator

- React
- Svelte
- Basic Python